VALERI GETSOV

Angular Developer

- **** 00359877770522
- www.linkedin.com/in/vgetsov
- Ruse, Bulgaria

- @ info@vgetsov.com
- https://getsov.dev/



EXPERIENCE

Hybrid Mobile Application Developer

Essence Group

iii 03/2022 - 07/2023 **♀**

Remote

Product Company

 Developing a hybrid mobile application from scratch, using the latest versions of Angular and Ionic for cosmetic niche needs

Full Stack Developer

Motion Software

= 08/2021 - 03/2022

Remote

Outsourcing Company

 Has been promoted to Full Stack MEAN Developer to maintain and add new features for the website of the same coaching company, adding ExpressJS, MongoDB and NodeJS to the Front End stack, which lead to about 50% increased coaching sessions sales

Front End Developer

Motion Software

= 05/2021 - 08/2021

Remote

Outsourcing Company

 Maintaining and building new features for a leading coaching company, using HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, jQuery, Angular, WordPress, PHP (for the WordPress needs), which lead to better UX and performance

Angular/Ionic Developer

Bulpont Ltd

= 01/2019 - 12/2020

Remote

Software company

- When my Angular training was certified, I was promoted to build and maintain a couple hybrid applications, using mainly lonic and Angular
- Used Ionic Pro (now named Appflow) for live deploying without the need to update the versions in the Play Store
- Was constantly improving my Ionic skills through Simon Grimm paid membership at ionicacademy.com
- Developed 5 apps (4 of which still live in Google Play), used by hundred of users

Front End Developer

Bulpont Ltd

= 05/2017 - 01/2019

Remote

Reilic

Software company

 Building and maintaining custom websites mainly for big Austrian companies, using mainly HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, jQuery

SUMMARY

Front End Developer with 6+ years of experience in building websites and hybrid mobile apps with great usability, less bounce rate, but higher conversion rate, using clean, reusable and well commented code.

Proficient with the tools and the technologies mentioned below in the Skills section.

Focused on how to improve my work and doing it the best way I can, while continuously looking for new ways to grow and expand my skill set.

Worked with big companies in Bulgaria, Austria, Israel and the United Kingdom, which lead to faster understanding and implementing the business goal, the main point and the details.

SKILLS

HTML5	CSS3	SS3 Java		t
jQuery	Angul	ar	lonic	
TypeScript Cord		ordova	ova Capacitor	
NodeJS	JS Express		JS MongoDB	
WordPres	ss O	penCa	rt SE	0
GitHub	BitBu	cket	Agile	Jira

FIND ME ONLINE



GitHub

https://github.com/Getsov



Stack Overflow

https://stackoverflow.com/users/870365 9/getsov



LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/vgetsov/

EXPERIENCE

Junior SEO Specialist

Netpeak

Digital Marketing Agency

- · Creating manual SEO Audits
- Inspecting On-page optimizations on clients websites and giving proposals for improvements
- · Keywords selections
- · Was promoted to Head of Off-page optimization
- All of that lead to increasing the organic search positions and client's revenue

TRAININGS

Upskill SalesForce Commerce Cloud

Telerik Academy, Remote

Accelerated ES6 JavaScript Training

Udemy, Remote

Agile Software Development

SoftUni, Bulgaria

Soft Skills for IT Professionals

SoftUni, Bulgaria

Ionic - Build iOS, Android & Web Apps with Ionic & Angular

Udemy, Remote

Angular Fundamentals

SoftUni, Bulgaria

ExpressJS Fundamentals

SoftUni, Bulgaria

JS Applications

SoftUni, Bulgaria

JS Advanced

SoftUni, Bulgaria

WordPress Basics

SoftUni, Bulgaria

Programming Fundamentals - Extended

SoftUni, Bulgaria

Web Fundamentals

SoftUni, Bulgaria

FIND ME ONLINE



Twitter

https://twitter.com/ValeriGetsov

EDUCATION

Upskill SalesForce Commerce Cloud

Telerik Academy, Remote

= 10/2021 - 03/2022

JavaScript Developer

SoftUni, Bulgaria

10/2016 - Present

Digital Marketing

SoftUni, Bulgaria

= 11/2016 - 08/2017

Master Degree Tourism and Travel Services Management

Tsenov Academy of Economics

= 09/2009 - 05/2014

LANGUAGES

Bulgarian

Native



English

Proficient



Spanish

Intermediate

